 2822 None
  837 No
  808 Vice Admiralty Court
  551 Yes
  523 British and Spanish
  321 British and Brazilian
  265 British and Portuguese
   51 British and Dutch
   27 N/A
   26 Vice Admiralty Court at St. Helena
   11 British Liberated African Department
   15 British Customs House
   13 Vice Admiralty Court at Cape of Good Hope
    8 Vice Admiralty Court at Sierra Leone
    4 British and Brazilian at Rio de Janiero
    4 British and Brazilian at Sierra Leone
    3 British and Portuguese at Sierra Leone
    5 British and French
    2 Yes, Spanish, Portugese, and Netherlands
    2 Yes at Sierra Leone
    2 Yes, Zanzibar
    1 British and United States
    1 Vice Admiralty Court at New Providence
    1 Colonial Secretary's Office, Liverpool
    1 Court of Admirality
    1 yes, Spanish and Brazillian
    1 Government House Dominica
    1 Vice Admiralty Court at Barbados
    1 British Vice Counsel at Bremen
    1 Yes at Cape of Good Hope
    1 Vice Admiralty Court at Mauritius
    1 Yes, HMS court at New york
    1 British and Egyptian
